01webdirectory.com 2017-12-01

# 01Webdirectory.com: Privacy Policy

  |  |   | **Home >> Privacy Policy** |    
---|---|---  
  |   |    
  |  |   |    
  |  |   |    
---|---  
  
01webdirectory.com understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide information about yourself in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at 01webdirectory.com more valuable to you. We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information 01webdirectory.com may collect how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use (the "TaCU") posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the TaCU. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the TCU.   
  
  |    
**01webdirectory.com and Cookies**  
  |    
  
Upon your first visit to 01webdirectory.com, 01webdirectory.com may send a "cookie" to your computer. Cookies are used by many sites, an internet search on 'cookies' may provide you with more information that you will ever need. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. 01webdirectory.com will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.  
  
  |    
  
Most internet browser are set up to accept cookie. Although it is possible to reset your computer settings to inform you of cookie or to reject cookies, such actions may interfere with your searches at 01webdirectory.com  
  
  |    
**What Information Do We Collect?**  
  |    
  
01webdirectory.com does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the site submission process. This information may be used to contact you if there is a need for a revision to your site reviews. 01webdirectory.com notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.  
  
  |    
**Links to Other Sites**  
  |    
  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by 01webdirectory.com searches are developed by people over whom 01webdirectory.com has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.  
  
  |    
**01webdirectory.com Shared Information**  
  |    
If you still have questions feel free to contact us.  
  |    
01webdirectory.com  
37/5, 2nd Floor  
Meanee Avenue, Tank Road.  
Ulsoor, Bangalore  
India – 560 042  
webmaster@01webdirectory.com  
  |    
   
  |  |    
---  
  
Computers & Internet: Communications & Networking, Education & Certification, Graphics & Multimedia, Hardware, Internet, Programming & Development, Software, Security & Encryption | Companies & Organizations: Agriculture, Education, Energy & Utilities, Engineering, Marketing & Advertising, Organizations, R & D, Real Estate, Recreation, Sports | Finance & Investment: **** Accounting & Auditing, Banking, Insurance | Health: Alternative Medicine, Diseases & Conditions, Medicine | Travel & Transportation: Automotive, Lodging & Accommodation, Transportation, Tour Operators |  Reference & Guides | Online Shopping & Services  

  |   |   |
